<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools">
    <!-- Array of assignment names -->
    <string-array name="assignment_names">
        <item>Assignment 1</item>
        <item>Assignment 2</item>
        <item>Assignment 3</item>
        <item>Assignment 4</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- Error messages -->
    <string name="action_assignment_invalid" tools:ignore="UnusedResources">The current assignment skeleton does not run assignment %d</string>

    <!-- Assignment html strings for About dialog -->
    <string-array name="about_assignments">
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            <h2>Android App Components and Data Persistence</h2>
            <h3>Assignment: 1</h3>
            <h3>Skeleton Version: 1.0</h3>
            <p>
                This assignment introduces the concept of <b>Intents</b>
                and shows how they can be used for a <b>one-way</b> exchange
                information between Android <b>Activities</b>.
            </p>
            ]]>
        </item>

        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            <h2>Android App Components and Data Persistence</h2>
            <h3>Assignment: 2</h3>
            <h3>Skeleton Version: 1.0</h3>
            <p>
                This assignment introduces the concept of using intents for <b>two-way</b>
                communication between Activities. It builds upon assignment 1 by
                starting the image <b>download activity for results</b>. The download
                image activity will have to be modified to return the downloaded image
                URL in a data intent so that the main activity will be able to display
                it in an image view widget.
            </p>
            ]]>
        </item>

        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            <h2>Android App Components and Data Persistence</h2>
            <h3>Assignment: 3</h3>
            <h3>Skeleton Version: 1.0</h3>
            <p>
                This assignment introduces the concept of using a <b>broadcast intent</b>
                for <b>two-way</b> communication between Activities. It builds upon
                assignment 1 by having the MainActivity register as a <b>local
                BroadcastReceiver</b>. The MainActivity then starts the DownloadActivity
                to download an image after which, the DownloadActivity returns this
                path to the downloaded image by broadcasting a result intent back to
                the MainActivity. The MainActivity then displays the received image
                file in an ImageView.
            </p>
            ]]>
        </item>

        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            <h2>Android App Components and Data Persistence</h2>
            <h3>Assignment: 4</h3>
            <h3>Skeleton Version: 1.0</h3>
            <p>
                Currently this assignment uses a ThreadPoolExecutor downloading
                policy.
            </p>
            ]]>
        </item>
    </string-array>
</resources>